Guide to the Emirates Bird Records Committee records AD.MC.057
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Other records (digital), 1993-2019; 28.6 Megabytes in 49 files
  - Reports: 20, 2000; 0.5 Megabytes in 9 files, PDF
    - The first record of Shikra...in the United Arab Emirates (Djerf, J. and E.) (Box Electronic records, E-records AD_MC_057_046)
    - The first records of Sooty Shearwaters...in the United Arab Emirates (Aspinall, S.) (Box Electronic records, E-records AD_MC_057_047)
    - Wire-tailed Swallow...: the first record for the United Arab Emirates (James, S.) (Box Electronic records, E-records AD_MC_057_048)
  - Reports: 21, 2001-2002; 0.6 Megabytes in 1 file, PDF
    - Emirates Bird Report, No. 21 (unpublished): Systematic list, March 2001 - October 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records AD_MC_057_049)
- Oversize [to be processed]
  - ENHG: Birds likely to be seen, by location and month, 1987
    - Abu Dhabi Island
    - Das Island
    - Al Ain
    - Tarif
    - Jebel Dhanna
    - Saadiyat
    - Zakum S-complex
    - Zarka Island
    - Liwa
    - Futaysi / Bahrani
    - Qarnain Island
    - Sweihan Road; Sweihan / Al Hair [sic]
    - Abu Dhabi - Dubai road
    - Dubai - Safa Park
    - Al Ain - Abu Dhabi road
    - Madam / Shwaib [sic]
    - Jebel Ali; Sir Abu Nu'air
    - Sharjah
    - Dhaid
    - Zibara; Idhn; Zubaya; Umm Shaif S-Complex
    - Ajman / Umm al Qawain
    - Hamriya / Jazirat al Hamra
    - Northern Emirates / Ras al Khaimah
    - Rams / Dhaya
    - Sham / Khor Khawwyr
    - Kharan / Digdaga
    - Masafi
    - Wadi al Bih / Wadi Hatta
    - Fujairah
    - Khor Kalba
    - Khor Fakkan
    - Dibba
    - Burami / Jebel Qatar [sic]
    - Jebel Ashker / Mahdah (Oman); Bidi al Ajam; Wadi Shimal
    - Wadi Fayd / Hatta
  - ENHG: Bird records; records list of all (compiled Sept. 1980, 299 pages), 1977-1980
  - ENHG: Bird records; records list of all (compiled April 1987, 448 pages), 1977-1985
  - ENHG: Bird record summary for 1979
  - ENHG: Bird record summary for 1980